sisweb.com 2014-06-21

# Privacy Policy

News:Join us at ASMS in Baltimore, June 15th-19th. We are booth #1! New catalog, NIST 14, and new products. New SIS 2014 catalog, Nanoliter MALDI/TOF dispensing, heater transfer tube for Thermo, NE300 syringe pump, ... 

The following terms apply to all public web sites (this Site) operated by Scientific Instrument Services, Inc., including [www.sisweb.com](http://www.sisweb.com/), [scientificmachining.com](http://scientificmachining.com/), and [simion.com](http://simion.com/).

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey, fill out a form or download software. 

Any data we request that is not required will be specified as voluntary or optional. 

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information, organization name, or billing information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

 **What do we use your information for?**

Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested by the customer. 

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

  * To process transactions  
The email address and/or phone you provide for order processing may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order or request.  

  * To personalize your experience  
Your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs. 
  * To improve our customer service and web site  
Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs. We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you. 
  * To send you our corporate newsletter or literature  
Upon submitting our mailing list update form or placing an order, you may also be subscribed to our corporate e-mail newsletter "S.I.S. Mass Spec Source" (distributed at most once, sometimes twice, a month), but you can unsubscribe to this at any time by clicking the "Unsubscribe" link in the e-mail. At times we have also done print mailings, and at any time you can request or unrequest our print catalog and other printed product literature, or change your address and contact information, via our mailing list update form. 

**How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or access your personal information. 

These security measures include: password protected directories and databases to safeguard your information, SSL (Secure Sockets Layered) technology to ensure that your information is fully encrypted and sent across the Internet securely or PCI Scanning to actively protect our servers from hackers and other vulnerabilities. 

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Database to be only accessed by those authorized with special access rights to our systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. 

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

 **Do we use cookies?**

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

 **Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

 **Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

 **California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

Users who register on our mailing list can make changes to their information at anytime via the http://www.sisweb.com/maillist.htm web page. Users who register on the simion.com discussion group can make changes to their information at anytime by clicking their name in the upper-right area of the discussion board and selecting 'My Profile'.

 **Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

 **CAN-SPAM Compliance**

We have taken the necessary steps to ensure that we are compliant with the CAN-SPAM Act of 2003 by never sending out misleading information.

 **Web Sites**

This policy also applies to all public web sites operated by Scientific Instrument Services, Inc., including www.sisweb.com, scientificmachining.com, and simion.com.

 **Terms and Conditions**

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at <http://www.sisweb.com/terms.htm>.

 **Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

 **Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. Policy changes will apply only to information collected after the date of the change. 

This policy was last modified on **June 13, 2012**.

 **Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. 

www.sisweb.com  
1027 Old York Rd  
Ringoes, NJ 08551-1054  
United States  
908-788-5550

 **Privacy Policy Customer Pledge**

We pledge to you, our customer, that we have made a dedicated effort to bring our privacy policy in line with the the following important privacy laws and initiatives:  
Federal Trade Commision Fair  
California Online Privacy Protection Act  
Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act  
Privacy Alliance  
Controlling the Assault of Non-Solicited Pornography and Marketing Act

If at anytime you have a cause that needs to be disputed please fill out the [Trust Guard Dispute Resolution form](http://secure.trust-guard.com/disputesystem/). 

Respectfully, 

Scientific Instrument Services, Inc.   
www.sisweb.com 

Send comments on this page
